[Love Has Fireworks]
[Episode 21]
My landlady.
What are we having for dinner tonight?
Aren't you trying to get in shape?
Ever heard of not eating after noon?
It'll help you get those abs.
Really?
I suggest, before you go on strike,
you take a look at this
and then decide.
Comrade Li Fei.
Aren't you going to
put your words together
and praise the person in front of you?
Osamu!
The front-row seat!
Thank you.
That's awesome, bro.
I really didn't treat you
so well for nothing.
Tell you what,
tomorrow I'll go to the market
and buy a bag of eggplants in bulk.
I'll cook for you...
What are you looking at?
A bag of eggplants in bulk?
Shut up.
I...
Delete your memory of what just happened.
Anything else?
Nothing.
Thanks.
Aren't you going home?
I'm not done yet.
Okay.
Great.
So far, of the nine hotels involved,
seven have made
public statements and responses.
Four international hotels
have adopted conservative solutions.
They closed the comments
on their official Weibo,
and claimed the video was fake.
Two also announced that they will sue
the Weibo blogger.
Are you... not feeling well?
Do you need me to continue reading?
What about Shan Li Fang?
As Vice President Liao's instructions,
we followed closely
behind the international hotels
and were the fifth
to release an open letter.
We didn't admit to the behaviors
in the video.
What is the situation now?
Currently...
I've been through it all.
Just spit it out.
This time,
it's a bit different from before.
Netizens are extremely angry.
They suspect the involved hotels
of dodging responsibility.
They also united the public
to launch a joint boycott
with a signature campaign
against these nine hotels.
How does this outfit look?
How many times have you paced
back and forth?
He's on stage, and you're in the audience.
He can't see you.
What do you mean he can't see me?
I will sit in the front row.
He often interacts with the audience
in the front two rows.
It's my first time meeting my idol,
of course I need to look my best.
You women,
when you see your idol,
you're more excited
than seeing your own husband.
That's totally different.
Alright, here you go.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking one back?
What do you mean?
Did you think both tickets were for you?
You are too greedy.
Do you know how hard it was
to get these two tickets?
What else?
I already made plans with someone.
Give the ticket...
Why?
If you took them all, then I...
Then I don't get to watch it?
Why would you watch it? Do you want to?
Didn't you say before
that you didn't even know him?
Aren't you interested? Give it to me.
No.
Give it to me.
I love him.
You know, getting these two tickets
has completely sucked me in.
I'm in too deep. I can't get out now.
Is that a problem?
Really?
Fine, we'll go together.
Are you even human?
Right, how much were these tickets?
You're talking about money
for our shared idol?
That's so tacky.
Just consider it
my New Year's gift to you.
That's too generous.
I still need to pay. How much is it?
If you insist on talking about money,
it's worth more than ten meals
of stir-fried eggplant strips.
Three meals at most.
Deal.
Three meals.
If it weren't for me taking care of them,
these flowers definitely
wouldn't be blooming so well now.
Exactly.
Our Shiyu is really good at
everything she does.
Even the flowers listen to you so well.
Let alone other things.
It seems this old man should make an exit
to give you young people
more time and space,
so you won't think
I'm a bother or in the way.
Hello, Chairman.
Why call him Chairman at home?
Call him Uncle Liao.
Hello, Uncle Liao.
You are not an old man.
You are the most handsome dad
in the universe.
Have a seat, Ruohai.
Such a sweet talker.
You always know how to make me happy.
Tell me.
You called me over, buttered me up first,
and now you're going to
tear into me, right?
I know you too well.
Let's cut to the chase.
The online public opinion
is overwhelming this time.
Is Shan Li Fang going to just sit
and wait for its demise?
Uncle Liao, you're exaggerating.
This incident may seem accidental,
but I personally think
someone did it on purpose.
There is an account called point three.
We looked into it.
It was cultivated for thirteen months
just for this one post today.
Of course, the companies involved
are mostly international hotel brands.
So I personally think
they are not targeting our Shan Li Fang.
Shan Li Fang is just collateral damage.
Therefore, this incident
shouldn't affect us too much.
Then,
about the joint boycott,
what's your take on that?
Netizens these days are
under too much pressure.
They are just using this incident
as an outlet to vent.
Time is the best medicine.
So the best strategy to solve this problem
is to do nothing.
You can't stump Ruohai.
It seems you've arranged everything.
Of course.
Naturally, Shan Li Fang
isn't doing absolutely nothing.
Internally, we must
investigate thoroughly.
Similar incidents cannot happen again.
Externally,
we have also formulated
various preferential policies.
Netizens are the most forgetful.
With these preferential policies,
our turnover will soon recover.
In summary, please rest assured, Chairman.
Our team
will definitely get through this crisis
as soon as possible.
Surprised?
Impressed?
Good.
Shiyu has grown up.
With Ruohai's support,
you can handle things on your own.
It seems this time
I was overly worried.
You were clearly worried
about the company,
yet you said
you missed me and wanted a family dinner
for the New Year.
As a father, seeing my daughter happy
is what matters the most.
Don't just focus on work.
Relationships, like work,
also require you to manage them with care.
I don't understand this.
Are you in a hurry to marry me off?
How could I bear to?
I haven't spoiled you enough.
Even if you marry,
it has to be to someone
who spoils you as much as I do.
There is definitely no such person.
Then I won't be able to get married.
With that sweet mouth, you always win.
[The play is fun. A small theater.]
This is a crosstalk.
Yes.
I'm very happy to lead you out
to perform for everyone.
Am I an animal?
Drag you up here?
Isn't that still an animal?
Pull you out?
Am I a corpse? Pull me out?
No, I mean they go down, you come up.
This is called...
That's called inviting me out.
Right.
Blowing you out.
Am I snot?
The ''invite'' as in "inviting you out".
Inviting you out
to continue performing for everyone.
Exactly.
This person here
is a very excellent loser.
No, wait, what?
Another slip of the tongue.
Actor.
Is it actor or loser?
Old loser.
Is "old loser" appropriate?
It is actor, just kidding.
Stop making jokes.
I like you.
Really?
Let me praise you.
Go ahead.
You are, in the entire crosstalk world,
the only head of
a very famous actor.
Alright, alright, alright.
So I'm still an animal.
That's poor wording.
What do you mean by "head"?
A head, a flock.
A duck?
A strip?
Am I a ribbonfish?
A pile? A puddle? A blob?
Fine. So I'm getting runnier and runnier?
Am I not even solid anymore?
No, I mean you are...
That should be "an actor".
Okay, okay, okay.
A very excellent actor.
Not at all.
This can be witnessed.
Look at all the friends here today.
Yes.
Not many like me.
No way.
Cute, right?
What a good guy.
A crosstalk show isn't lively
without jokes and laughter.
Yes.
We master four skills:
speaking, imitating, teasing, and singing,
just to bring you joy.
How about this? You give us an imitation
in front of our friends.
Try an imitation right here?
Can you?
No problem.
Imitate something flying in the sky.
Flying in the sky?
Like what?
A plastic bag.
This silly girl,
how can she ignore me?
What's so good about this guy?
[The play is fun. A small theater.]
Sir, I like you so much.
[Crosstalk is all about
speaking, imitating, teasing and singing.]
Okay, come here.
Sir, I really like you.
Okay, thanks, thanks.
Okay, come on, let's take a group photo.
We'll take a picture together later.
Okay, come on.
Okay, thanks, thanks, thanks.
Um, Osamu, I've liked you for a long time.
Let's take a picture.
Okay, no problem.
Great, great.
One more, one more.
Okay, okay.
[The play is fun. A small theater.]
I finally get a photo,
and you make me look so ugly.
Who said that? Look at Osamu.
-See, Osamu looks great.
-Osamu is so cute.
I'm so happy today! I'm so excited!
What about you? What about you?
And you?
Me too. I'm so happy!
-I finally met Osamu!
-Right? Right?
I'm so...
Hopeless.
What did you say?
I'm saying Osamu is so
inspiring and talented.
I like him so much.
I... I... I...
Yeah, unlike you,
pretending to be a rich second-gen.
Hey, what do you mean by that?
Biting the hand that feeds you?
Who got the tickets for you? Forgot?
You! Thank you, thank you!
Tell you what,
let's go get some drinks tonight,
since we don't have work tomorrow.
Have a drink. It's fine if we get drunk.
You're actually asking for a drink.
Watch your image.
Osamu!
Hurry up.
Thank you.
This is absolutely the best gift
I've received this year.
I'll be happy for the whole next year.
You're welcome.
But I seem to remember
someone told me
as long as I get the ticket,
she'd take my last name.
Am I right?
You actually misheard.
I said I would change my last name,
but I didn't say whose last name
I would take.
You're playing word games, huh?
Playing dirty, huh?
You're the one
who daydreamed and misinterpreted it.
Who's to blame?
Fine.
It's fine if you don't take my last name.
But you have to change
your last name anyway.
So, what will it be?
I'll give you a choice:
Tan.
Tan Fei. How about that?
Flick away, flick away!
I'll flick you away! Flick you away!
How about Wang Fei? Change it to Wang.
Wang Fei is not bad.
I actually quite like Wang Fei.
If that really doesn't work,
how about...
I'll just take my dad's last name.
Aren't you already taking
your dad's last name?
No.
Then whose last name do you have?
Your mom's?
Yes. I changed my last name before.
Really?
Then what was your name before?
Su Fei.
Su Fei?
I knew it! Laugh all you want.
It's because you guys
kept laughing and humiliating me
that I was forced to change my name.
To change this name back then,
do you know how much
determination it took?
This is absolutely
the bravest decision
I've ever made in my life.
I said back then,
if I didn't change my name,
I wouldn't go to college.
So, this name
carries so much blood and tears.
However,
after I changed my name,
it was still no good.
I found I couldn't save money, you know?
You know? Qian Fei, Qian Fei.
Do you know why?
"Owe fee."
The money either flies away
or gets owed out.
How could I keep it?
When you changed your last name back then,
why didn't you change your first name too?
It'd be so nice to be called Qian Lai.
No, my dad said
my name was calculated
by a fortune-teller.
Based on the Five Elements,
he said I was missing...
I don't remember.
Anyway, he said I couldn't change it.
I know.
I think
in your Five Elements,
you're missing a brain cell.
You're the one missing a brain cell!
I'll kick you to death.
Kick you to death, I swear!
Want to kick me?
Brainless.
Did you take
my golden advice to heart?
Your phone is ringing.
[Jinzi]
Hello, Jinzi.
What's wrong?
Figure out how to pay you back?
Not yet, it's another thing.
So many romantic prospects.
Thank you.
He even closes the door,
who wants to listen anyway?
Where are you going?
Going on a date this late?
A date? What date? I have business to do.
Um, you've been drinking, so don't drive.
Got it.
Wait.
Um...
Be nice to her.
Talk nicely,
don't lose your temper easily.
Unless she's like me,
I really have no rent to refund you
and put up with living with you.
What are you talking about?
Don't lock the door.
I'll be right back.
You're not staying out all night?
Fei Fei.
Being in love really makes a difference.
One second we were talking fine,
and the next,
he just up and leaves.
So much for loyalty to friends.
Why do I feel a little upset?
[Dad]
Hello, Dad.
It's so late, you're still up?
Your mom's in emergency surgery right now.
Can you come back tomorrow?
What happened?
Wasn't her condition already stable?
Your mom heard that
you and Qian Fei broke up,
[Surgery Staff]
and her blood pressure shot up.
Tonight, she suddenly had chest pain.
I took her to the hospital,
and the checkup showed
the main artery in her heart
is 90% blocked.
They went straight into emergency surgery.
Okay, I got it.
Look,
I'll book the first flight back tomorrow.
I'm booking now. Gotta go.
[Qian Fei]
[Wang Ruohai]
Wang Ruohai?
Hello?
Qian Fei.
Let me ask you something.
Did you tell my mom
that we broke up?
Of course not.
I called to check in
on your mom's health.
But
it seemed you didn't tell them the truth.
So I made an excuse.
Qian Fei.
We've already broken up.
Could you please stop showing concern
for my mom in your own way?
My mom doesn't need it.
None of my family needs it.
I'm telling you, Qian Fei,
my mom doesn't need
your hypocritical care.
If you have any conscience,
stay away from my family
from now on, okay?
What are you talking about?
Li Yifei, why are you here?
Hang up the phone first.
Hello? Hello?
Didn't Li Yifei go to see a girl?
Why did he go to Wang Ruohai's place?
Bastard.
The number you have dialed is...
[Qian Fei]
You've hit me,
and vented your anger.
Let's talk.
Why did you beat me up?
Why did I beat you up?
Do you know what two kinds of men
I hate the most?
First,
those who play dirty tricks
behind people's backs.
Second,
those who step on their women
to climb the ladder.
You're both.
You edited the video so well.
Who else should I beat up if not you?
What's the relationship between you two?
None of your business.
I'm warning you for the last time.
If you dare to mess with Qian Fei again,
it won't be as simple as a beating.
You're still awake?
You're back.
What do you mean? This is my home.
Where else would I go?
Wait, wait.
What happened to your face?
That girl was so hard to deal with,
you know?
A few words in and she messed up my face.
Can you believe it?
Young people nowadays are
really not to be messed with.
So that's your type?
Your taste is getting
more and more particular.
Like it or not,
I might as well try more while I'm young.
At least I won't have regrets
when I'm old.
Hey, come here.
Your face
looks like you've been
constipated for a week.
Just spit it out.
Don't hold it in.
Are you trying to ask me how things went
with that girl?
Are you just curious,
or a little jealous?
You went to see Wang Ruohai.
Impressive.
You found out so quickly
that I went on a date
with your ex-boyfriend?
You guys fought?
I just couldn't stand
seeing my landlady get bullied.
That's it. Simple as that.
Well, wait here.
Let me treat your wound.
No need, it's just a minor injury.
It doesn't hurt at all.
You didn't even see what he looked like.
No need to treat it.
No, no, no.
It doesn't hurt at all.
[The surgery was a success.
Your mom is fine.]
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I barely dare to touch it.
Be gentle, it hurts.
Bear with it.
Be gentle, it really hurts.
Feeling better?
Oh my god.
Hang in there, just one more.
One more? There's more?
I need to disinfect it again.
Don't move. Don't move.
Seriously, do not move.
The more you move, the more it hurts.
♪ No need to guess the ending
right from the beginning ♪
♪ Let the melody play
among the chords and the wind ♪
♪ And no need to demand
that yesterday keeps its promises ♪
♪ Leave some surprises in life
to the unknown ♪
♪ There's no need to make a judgment
based on a few past ♪
♪ Somehow I feel a little disappointed
That's why I create poems ♪
♪ There's no need
to give up for the past ♪
Well...
Okay, that's... that's enough.
Go on.
♪ I need some courage to get praises ♪
Get some sleep.
Yes, it's done.
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
Thanks for today.
For standing up for me.
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
And also, thank you
for spending New Year's Eve with me.
♪ Dumb shoulder Like a harbor
waiting for you ♪
Are you drunk?
Today is the 30th. Tomorrow is the 31st.
The day after tomorrow is New Year's Day.
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
Yeah, I got it wrong.
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
Well... then tomorrow night,
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
you'll be spending New Year's
with your friends, right?
Landlady,
how about tomorrow
you make me stir-fried eggplant strips?
I'll come back early.
Then we can have dinner together,
and watch the news.
This way, neither of us
♪ Also, there's no need
to force the closest bonds ♪
has to spend the New Year alone.
Okay.
Sure.
♪ I might be left alone,
but I have your warmth ♪
Um...
Well, good night. Get some sleep.
Good night.
♪ And there's no need to dwell
on right or wrong—not because of fear ♪
♪ A hug far outweighs endless apologies ♪
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
Suddenly I feel like
this winter
♪ Dumb shoulder Like a harbor
waiting for you ♪
is the warmest winter I've had
in all my years in Shanghai.
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
Good night.
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
[Zela Dance Studio]
It's just a demonstration for everyone.
Don't be nervous.
Right.
Okay, let's start.
Thank you for coming
to our open house today.
Zela Dance Studio
is a dance studio
specializing in hip-hop dance.
Since many of our senior friends
are also interested in learning,
[Zela Dance Studio]
we've specially arranged
a demonstration session today.
We have both hip-hop and square dance
for you to choose from.
Let's start with hip-hop.
Music.
It's this teacher.
My friend took private lessons with her,
and won first prize
in the senior group last year.
Really?
My grandson is her student now.
He was chosen as the president
of the dance club at his school.
Amazing! So good!
She dances really well.
That rhythm is even more intense
than square dancing.
Please fill in your name, phone number,
-and the course you'd like to enroll in.
-You danced so well.
Can I learn it?
-Your phone number and the course
-Of course you can.
-you'd like to enroll in.
-Anyone can learn it.
-I think that...
-As for private lessons,
-we should learn square dance.
-I think...
You can take a look first.
-What's the key?
-The key is
-I've been quite thorough in analysis
-to see whether you have...
of dance movements.
-I'll add extra classes.
-Yeah. Right.
For instance, when I give extra lessons,
they're all free.
Make-up lessons are free.
Right, I think here's the thing:
-if you don't get it in the first class...
-You can ask first if you can book.
Ms. Yu.
Book a trial class.
I want to learn dance from you
with my grandson,
but my lower back isn't good.
Your lower back isn't good?
Right.
Look, if your lower back isn't good,
you definitely shouldn't do
that dance style.
Because
that dance has very intense music.
It's really hard on your lower back.
For my grandson, I can bear it.
You obviously don't have a grandson,
you wouldn't understand.
No, I'm telling you.
Whether you have a grandson or not
has nothing to do with your lower back.
-I mean you don't understand my feelings.
-Auntie. Auntie.
-Auntie. Auntie. Don't!
-I want to sign up...
Don't be angry, listen to me.
Here's the thing.
Given the condition of your lower back,
I really don't recommend you
learn dance from me.
But our square dance room
is right next to mine.
-Really?
-If you want to accompany your grandson,
you can take square dancing
and still be with him.
And the class is on the same day.
How does that sound?
That works. You have a way with words.
It's all about mutual understanding.
That teacher was also looking out for you.
I speak without thinking sometimes.
I'll go sign up now.
Yes, go sign up first.
I'll head over, okay?
Go sign up.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
Ms. Yu just told me about it.
I'll just sign up with you.
I'd be happy to have you sign up.
What's your name?
My name is Fang...
Ying, the "Ying" that means novel.
Right.
Jingjing.
Jingjing, it's me.
Fei.
Do you know where Jingjing went?
Okay, okay.
[See you at the internet cafe later.]
Where do you live?
How about we drop you off first?
I live farther than you,
let's drop you off first.
[I'll send you the location later.]
Thank you for earlier.
It's nothing. Just telling the truth.
Have you been learning dance
since childhood?
Yes, in Yunnan, people of all ages
love singing and dancing from a young age.
If you have a chance to visit again,
you might even fall in love with it.
I think the air and scenery in Yunnan
are indeed quite good.
But I feel that in every aspect,
compared to Shanghai...
I'm just telling the truth.
Okay, does the top look empty to you?
Should we add some balloons or something?
I don't think that's necessary.
No need for the top.
Just leave it as it is.
-Okay, sure.
-Adding more might not be safe anyway.
-Okay.
-In case something falls off.
Brother-in-law is here.
Go over it on your end.
Jingjing.
What are you doing here?
I went to your place to look for you,
but you weren't there.
Qian Fei said you were here.
Forgive me.
Can we go somewhere else to talk?
I'm very busy right now.
Just a moment,
just a moment.
I dissolved the company.
You were right.
I've been reflecting on this lately.
Before, I was busy
with my startup every day,
caught up in company matters,
and I neglected our life together.
But during that time, I didn't know.
I thought,
I thought that was everything to me.
But after calming down,
I realized that
the most important thing is you.
So,
after dissolving the company,
I don't want anything else,
I just want to be with you.
Aren't you going to hold on
until the product is developed
and launched?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong before.
Will you forgive me?
♪ Whenever I look up ♪
Jingjing.
After closing the company,
♪ I ran into your eyes ♪
I might not have much money.
In the short term,
I can't give you a luxury house or car,
but I will work hard
to make your life worry-free.
♪ Trying to catch that pleasant light ♪
From now on, I'll put you first,
put our life first.
So, Jingjing,
♪ To embrace that fleeting moment
of happiness ♪
will you marry me?
♪ Sometimes I cry,
and sometimes I'm happy ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel
I've captured the sweetness ♪
♪ Sometimes, I run,
and sometimes, I fall ♪
I don't mind that you have no money.
♪ Sometimes I feel
that having you is the best thing ♪
I don't mind that your startup failed.
♪ I've never loved anyone
like I love you ♪
But I don't want to marry you.
I'm sorry.
♪ Without any hesitation ♪
♪ I've never been loved like you love me ♪
♪ In short, I'll wait for my love ♪
♪ I've never seen a bright sea like you ♪
♪ Every minute is colorful ♪
♪ I've never experienced
such a warm love as yours ♪
♪ In short, I won't let go of my hand ♪
You're back.
Such a feast!
Here, give it to me.
Hello?
Fei, come keep me company.
Just now,
Lu Ze proposed to me again,
and I turned him down.
Okay, okay, I'll be right there.
Well,
I can't make stir-fried eggplant strips
for you today.
You can eat out with your girlfriend.
What?
I'll spend tonight with someone else.
Don't wait up for me.
Hold on, hold on.
What? What girlfriend? I...
Stood me up?
Fine.
Unbelievable.
Stood me up.
Hey, let's ring in the New Year
together tonight!
Hoes over bros.
What kind of people are these?
Hey, organize a gathering.
Let's celebrate New Year's Eve
together tonight.
Li Yifei.
You called me back late last night saying
no gathering tonight.
And now you're telling me
the gathering is back on.
Jerk.
Are you just banking on me
not cutting ties with you?
Alright, alright.
Stop it.
I'm not in a good mood right now.
What's wrong? What happened?
Who pissed you off?
Stop asking. Just gather the guys.
Round everyone up.
Let's get wild tonight!
I'm so exhausted.
When I told Lu Ze
that I wouldn't marry him,
I just felt completely drained.
What is happening to me?
[In the next episode
of "Love Has Fireworks"]
Alright.
Happy New Year.
Good night.
They're fighting.
Stop, stop!
Don't. Don't open the door.
What's going on?
I just have to capture a moment like this.
What are you doing? I'm already like this.
Cross-arm toast!
No, no.
I'm a guy.
It's fine if you joke about me.
But don't joke about Jinzi.
She's a girl.
-I don't mind.
-Right?